This is a quick demo of my recent project an ASP.NET Online Calculator developed in C#.
The goal of the project was to convert the desktop version into a web application using ASP.NET technology.
In process of building the application I have
used C#, ASP.NET, Bootstrap and JavaScript
languages.
The code from the desktop version was reused in the code behind file in order to build the Logic Layer.
As normal the user can perform standard
maths including negative and percentage
calculations.
From security perspective all of the information that the user sets while using the application is encrypted and
on each post back of the page the neccessary
information is used to complete each operation.
On error handling I am using code behind to
catch the exception and also JavaScript to
notify the user of what options they have.
Here speaking of User Experience and providing Responsive Design for the app is hapening through Bootstrap implementation.
Meaning that by changing the size of the display most of the content changes its location on the page for best presentation possible.
If this project opened a topic for discussion please do not hesitate to contact me at getintouch@yordan.co.uk
or by visitingwww.yordan.co.uk/get-in-touch/
Thank you for watching